============================================================
Part 1(a): Single Agent, Single Task
============================================================

Parameters:
  Number of agents (R): 1
  Number of tasks (T): 1
  Task radius (Tr): 50
  Required agents per task (Tc): 1
  Agent speed (Rv): 25
  Iterations: 1000

Running simulation...
D:\study_n_docs\SMU\mas\succ_claude\a3_mas_v1_cl_m2\models\sta_model.py:44: UserWarning: You are trying to set model.agents. In a next release, this attribute is used by MESA itself so you cannot use it directly anymore.Please adjust your code to use a different attribute name for custom agent storage
  self.agents = []

Results:
  Total tasks completed: 0
  Average tasks per iteration: 0.0000

Plot saved to: results/part1a_results.png

============================================================
ANALYSIS:
============================================================

Movement Model:
- Used uniform random walk: random angle [0, 2π] and random distance [0, Rv]
- This ensures agent explores the space uniformly over time
- Boundary reflections keep agent within [0, 1000] × [0, 1000]

Performance Metric Analysis:
- Tasks completed per iteration is binary (0 or 1) for single agent
- This creates a noisy, discrete signal
- Average completion rate gives better steady-state performance measure
- Cumulative completion shows overall system efficiency

Is this a good measure?
- For single agent: YES for average rate, but per-iteration is too noisy
- Better metrics could include:
  * Average time between task completions
  * Spatial coverage efficiency
  * Expected task completion time from spawn